<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Jacks Pino</title>
    <link>/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Jacks Pino</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Jacks Pino - jap6527 - SDS 348 - 12/11/2020  Introduction I chose to use data I found on gapminder.org, which has a plethora of data of the world&#39;s countries. The variables I chose to look at in particular were the following: fertility rate, child mortality rate, food supply, the proportion of billionaires, the proportion of those who have access to basic sanitation, population density, and the rate of inflation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Jacks Pino - jap6527 - SDS 348 - 10/19/2020 Introduction For my exploratory data analysis, I chose to use the data I previously used for my SDS 328M final project last semester. For my final project last semester, I had manually combined different datasets to determine if there was any relationship between the rate of HIV in a given county, its urbanization status or setting (meaning if it was rural or urban), and the percentage of disconnected youth (meaning the percentage of people ages 16-19 that were not in school or employed).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HW 8</title>
      <link>/project/hw8/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/hw8/</guid>
      <description>Jacks Pino, jap6527  Question 1 We will analyze some data from a famous case of alleged gender discrimination in admission to graduate programs at UC Berkeley in 1973. The three variables are Admit (Admitted, Rejected), Gender (Male, Female), and Dept (Departments A, B, C, D, E, F). First, create a dichotomous outcome variable \(y\) that is 1 if Admit==&amp;quot;Admitted&amp;quot; and 0 otherwise.
1.1 (2 pts) Predict \(y\) from Gender using a logistic regression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HW 9</title>
      <link>/project/hw9/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/hw9/</guid>
      <description>Enter your name and EID here This homework is due on Sunday Nov 15, 2020 at 11:59pm. Please submit as an HTML file on Canvas.
For all questions, include the R commands/functions that you used to find your answer. Answers without supporting code will not receive credit.
 Review of how to submit this assignment All homework assignments will be completed using R Markdown. These .Rmd files consist of text/syntax (formatted using Markdown) alongside embedded R code.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
